<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>English on NekoRAM7</title>
        <link>https://PureWhite216.github.io/tags/english/</link>
        <description>Recent content in English on NekoRAM7</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://PureWhite216.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Academic Writing in English</title>
        <link>https://PureWhite216.github.io/p/academic-writing-in-english/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://PureWhite216.github.io/p/academic-writing-in-english/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://PureWhite216.github.io/p/academic-writing-in-english/Image.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Academic Writing in English" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is a note of my English course in Grade 1, which concentrates on &lt;code&gt;Thesis Statement&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Six Principle of Academic Writing&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;thesis-statement-the-core-of-academic-writing&#34;&gt;Thesis Statement, the Core of Academic Writing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;main-point&#34;&gt;Main Point&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thesis Statement should clearly demonstrate author’s position, which means one aspect most overwhelms the other one, and there should be only one idea in TS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;steps-to-generate-a-thesis-statement&#34;&gt;Steps to Generate a Thesis Statement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Topic&lt;/code&gt;: Problem posed by drug addiction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Your interest&lt;/code&gt;: The problem of crack babies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;General subject&lt;/code&gt;: Crack babies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Narrow the topic&lt;/code&gt;: Programs for crack kids.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Take a position on the the topic&lt;/code&gt;:Have a target, Take a position and Give an idea, such as
&amp;ldquo;More attention should be paid to the environment crack kids grow up in.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Use specific language&lt;/code&gt;: Experts estimate that half of crack babies will grow up in home environments lacking rich cognitive and emotional stimulation.(More specific)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Make an assertion based on clearly stated support&lt;/code&gt;: Because half of all crack babies are likely to grow up in homes lacking good cognitive and emotional stimulation, the federal governments should finance programs to supplement parental care for crack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;The thesis answers the question&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-tips&#34;&gt;Other Tips&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good thesis statement often express a writer’s opinion or attitude on a particular topic.
Example:
Learning to play many musical instruments when I was young helped(How does the author fell) me to become a more intelligent and well-rounded person.(Body: how and why)
use specific verb to show your attitude(such as affect)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listing sub-topics or supporting ideas can make the TS more specific. Sub-ideas are parts of the TS.
Example1:
Some of the most serious problems in today’s countryside schools are the overcrowded classrooms, the los percentage of trained teachers, and the lack of resources such as textbooks for students.
Example2:
Th large influx of people to California has had major effects on the ability of the state to provide housing, electricity and jobs for all residents.(how)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t state the obivious, like “This essay will discuss&amp;hellip;” or “I an going to talk about”.
Long-term drug use can have disastrous effects on one’s marriage career, and health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example1&#34;&gt;Example1&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the Internet is filled with tremendous marketing potential, companies should exploit this potential by using web pages that offer both advertising and customer support.
&lt;code&gt;(TS indicates the logic development.)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example2&#34;&gt;Example2&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because Banana Herb Tea Supplement promotes rapid weight loss that results in the loss of muscle and lean body mass, it poses a potential danger to customers. (Indicates we shouldn’t)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example3&#34;&gt;Example3&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While most American families would view consanguineal marriage as a threat to the nuclear family structure, many Iranian families, like my own, believe that these marriage help reinforce kinship ties in an extended family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example4&#34;&gt;Example4&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the Internet is filled with tremendous marketing potential, companies should exploit this potential by using web pages that offer both advertising and customer support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example5&#34;&gt;Example5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hunger persists in Appalachia because jobs are scarce and farming in the infertile soil is rarely profitable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example6&#34;&gt;Example6&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While both Northerners and Southerners believed they fought against tyranny and oppression Northerners focused on the oppression of slaves while Southerners defend their property and self-government.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example7&#34;&gt;Example7&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through its contrasting river and shore scenes, Twain’s Huckleberry Finn suggests that to find the true expression of American democratic ideals, one must leave” civilized” society and go back to nature.&lt;code&gt;(Thesis statement is the result of comparison, not the procedure)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;six-principle-of-academic-writing&#34;&gt;Six Principle of Academic Writing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;objecivity&#34;&gt;Objecivity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;main-point-1&#34;&gt;Main Point&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Express your opinion indirectly with objective facts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;tips&#34;&gt;Tips&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;State natural and social phenomena which exist objectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Observation experiment description analysis and discussion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid personal emotion and subjective assumption&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-verbal expressions such as data, symbol, chart, and table are furthest int contrast colloquial expressions are forbidden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first and the second person are avoided and the passive voice is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Informal abbreviations that are typical of spoken language are not used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neutral and impersonal words are advocated in order to shun personal emotion effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;explicitness&#34;&gt;Explicitness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;use-signal-words&#34;&gt;Use Signal Words&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example1-1&#34;&gt;Example1&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moreover&lt;/strong&gt;, NMR has become an proven instrument for metabolic and structural studies in biology&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;example2-1&#34;&gt;Example2&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However&lt;/strong&gt;, a serious and partly insurmountable obstacle for superconducting magnets is the critical magnetic field that can be achieved without loss of the superconductivity.
(The idea is different from the former one)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;logical-conjunctions&#34;&gt;Logical Conjunctions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Undertake relationships&lt;/code&gt;: also, and, first, second, third.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;: near (to), far(from), in front of behind, beyond above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Time&lt;/code&gt;: now, then&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Comparison&lt;/code&gt;: in the same way, just like, just at&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Transition&lt;/code&gt;: but, still, yet, however, nevertheless, on the contrary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Stress&lt;/code&gt;: in fact, indeed, surely, necessarily, certainly, above all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Results and reasons&lt;/code&gt;: because, since, so, as a result, then, thus, otherwise,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Explanation&lt;/code&gt;: for example, in fact, in the case, for actually, for instance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;For this reason&lt;/code&gt;, for this purpose, so that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Summary&lt;/code&gt;: in a word, above all,  all in all, finally, at last, in conclusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;complexity&#34;&gt;Complexity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;complicated sentence pattern&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nominalization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lexical complexity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hence, it is not strange that (1)the interventional cardiologists had to face (3)unknown problems (2)emerging during their initial applications such as the late recoil (2)caused by the fast absorption of the scaffold the focal mechanical failure and the difficulties (2)noted in (2)controlling the drug release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
